[{"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"FailedTestCase","user":"derektd2@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        List current = this;\n        while (current != null) {\n            current = current.next;\n        }\n        current = new List(newValue);\n        return;\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244124,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":""},
  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"RuntimeError","user":"dbumpus2@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        if (next == null) {\n            next = new List(newValue);\n        }\n        next.addToEnd(newValue);\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244568,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":""},
  
  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"CompilerError","user":"mfeng22@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        if (this == null) {\n            this = new List(newValue);\n        }\n        if (this.next != null) {\n            this.next = new List(newValue);\n        } else {\n            this.next.addToEnd(newValue);\n        }\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244011,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":"/base/src/main/java/List.java:22: error: cannot assign to 'this'\n            this = new List(newValue);\n            ^\n1 error\n\nException in thread \"main\" org.testng.TestNGException: \nCannot load class from file: -configfailurepolicy\n\tat org.testng.internal.ClassHelper.fileToClass(ClassHelper.java:521)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.configure(TestNG.java:1354)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.privateMain(TestNG.java:1315)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.main(TestNG.java:1294)"},

  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"CompilerError","user":"mfeng22@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        if (this.next != null) {\n            this.next = List(newValue);\n        } else {\n            this.next.addToEnd(newValue);\n        }\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524243905,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":"/base/src/main/java/List.java:22: error: cannot find symbol\n            this.next = List(newValue);\n                        ^\n  symbol:   method List(int)\n  location: class List\n1 error\n\nException in thread \"main\" org.testng.TestNGException: \nCannot load class from file: -configfailurepolicy\n\tat org.testng.internal.ClassHelper.fileToClass(ClassHelper.java:521)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.configure(TestNG.java:1354)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.privateMain(TestNG.java:1315)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.main(TestNG.java:1294)"},

  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"FailedTestCase","user":"mfeng22@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        if (this.next != null) {\n            this.next = new List(newValue);\n        } else {\n            this.next.addToEnd(newValue);\n        }\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524243930,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":""},

  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"CompilerError","user":"mfeng22@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        if (this == null) {\n            this.Value = newValue;\n        }\n        if (this.next != null) {\n            this.next = new List(newValue);\n        } else {\n            this.next.addToEnd(newValue);\n        }\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244057,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":"/base/src/main/java/List.java:22: error: cannot find symbol\n            this.Value = newValue;\n                ^\n  symbol: variable Value\n1 error\n\nException in thread \"main\" org.testng.TestNGException: \nCannot load class from file: -configfailurepolicy\n\tat org.testng.internal.ClassHelper.fileToClass(ClassHelper.java:521)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.configure(TestNG.java:1354)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.privateMain(TestNG.java:1315)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.main(TestNG.java:1294)"},

  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"FailedTestCase","user":"mfeng22@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        if (this == null) {\n            this.value = newValue;\n        }\n        if (this.next != null) {\n            this.next = new List(newValue);\n        } else {\n            this.next.addToEnd(newValue);\n        }\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244065,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":""},

  {"score":1,"mode":"Exam","result":"CorrectSolution","user":"mfeng22@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        if (this == null) {\n            this.value = newValue;\n        }\n        if (this.next == null) {\n            this.next = new List(newValue);\n        } else {\n            this.next.addToEnd(newValue);\n        }\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244191,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":"correct"},

  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"RuntimeError","user":"derektd2@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        List current = this;\n        while (current != null) {\n            current = current.next;\n        }\n        current.next = new List(newValue);\n        return;\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244203,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":""},

  {"score":1,"mode":"Exam","result":"CorrectSolution","user":"yangm2@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        List curr = this;\n        while (curr.next != null) {\n            curr = curr.next;\n        }\n        curr.next = new List(newValue);\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244220,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":"correct"},

  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"CheckstyleError","user":"haoming5@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        if (this != null) {\n        while (this.next = null) {\n            this.next = new List(newValue);\n        }\n        }\n        return;\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244280,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":""},

  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"CheckstyleError","user":"haoming5@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        List list = new List(newValue);\n        if (this != null) {\n        while (this.next = null) {\n            this.next = list;\n        }\n        }\n        return;\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244359,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":""},

  {"score":1,"mode":"Exam","result":"CorrectSolution","user":"xingyub2@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        if (this.next == null) {\n            this.next = new List(newValue);\n            return;\n        }\n        next.addToEnd(newValue);\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244388,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":"correct"},

  {"score":1,"mode":"Exam","result":"CorrectSolution","user":"dbumpus2@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Return true if any subarray (OK, column or row) of the 2D array sums to the\n * passed argument n, false otherwise.\n *\n * You can assume that the input array is rectangular.\n */\npublic static boolean sumToN(final int[][] input, final int n) {\n    int sum = 0;\n    for (int i = 0; i < input.length; i++) {\n        for (int j = 0; j < input[i].length; j++) {\n            sum += input[i][j];\n        }\n        if (sum == n) {\n            return true;\n        }\n        sum = 0;\n    }\n    for (int j = 0; j < input[0].length; j++) {\n        for (int i = 0; i < input.length; i++) {\n            sum += input[i][j];\n        }\n        if (sum == n) {\n            return true;\n        }\n        sum = 0;\n    }\n    return false;\n}","timestamp":1524244364,"question":"Sp18_Q11_13","feedback":"correct"},

  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"FailedTestCase","user":"haoming5@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        List list = new List(newValue);\n        if (this != null) {\n        while (this.next == null) {\n            this.next = list;\n        }\n        }\n        return;\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244385,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":""},

  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"FailedTestCase","user":"haoming5@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        List list = new List(newValue);\n        if (this != null) {\n        while (this.next == null) {\n            this.next = list;\n            list.next = null;\n        }\n        }\n        return;\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244455,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":""},

  {"score":0,"mode":"Exam","result":"CompilerError","user":"derektd2@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for storing the last ten integers added.\n *\n * Your class should be named LastTen.\n *\n * Your class should implement two public methods as described below:\n * 1. void add(int newValue):\n *    add a new integer to the values that we are rememebring\n * 2. int[] getLastTen():\n *    return the last ten values that were added using add, in any order.\n *    If fewer than ten values were added, you should return zeros in their\n *    place.\n *\n * Examples:\n *   1. add(1), add(2)\n *      getLastTen: [1, 2, 0, 0, 0, ... ]\n *   2. add(0), add(1), add(2), ... add(10)\n *      getLastTen: [1, 2, 3, 4, ... 10]\n *\n * Your class should also provide a constructor that takes no arguments.\n */\n\n\n class LastTen {\n     private int counter = 0;\n     private int[] lastTen = new int[10];\n     public void add(int newValue) {\n         lastTen[counter%10] = newValue;\n         counter++;\n     }\n     public int[] getLastTen();\n     return lastTen;\n }","timestamp":1524244673,"question":"Sp18_Q11_11","feedback":"/base/src/main/java/LastTen.java:32: error: illegal start of type\n     return lastTen;\n     ^\n/base/src/main/java/LastTen.java:32: error: <identifier> expected\n     return lastTen;\n                   ^\n2 errors\n\nException in thread \"main\" org.testng.TestNGException: \nCannot load class from file: -configfailurepolicy\n\tat org.testng.internal.ClassHelper.fileToClass(ClassHelper.java:521)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.configure(TestNG.java:1354)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.privateMain(TestNG.java:1315)\n\tat org.testng.TestNG.main(TestNG.java:1294)"},

  {"score":1,"mode":"Exam","result":"CorrectSolution","user":"xingyub2@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Return true if the array is sorted in descending order, false otherwise.\n */\npublic static boolean isSorted(final int[] array) {\n    for (int i = 1; i < array.length; i++) {\n        if (array[i] > array[i - 1]) {\n            return false;\n        }\n    }\n    return true;\n}","timestamp":1524244673,"question":"Sp18_Q11_12","feedback":"correct"},

  {"score":1,"mode":"Exam","result":"CorrectSolution","user":"dbumpus2@illinois.edu","code":"/**\n * Class for representing a linked list of ints.\n */\npublic class List {\n    public int value;\n    public List next;\n\n    public List() { }\n\n    public List(final int setValue) {\n        value = setValue;\n    }\n\n    /**\n     * Add a value as the last item in the list.\n     *\n     * Can be called on any item of the list, although will normally be called\n     * on the first item.\n     */\n    public void addToEnd(final int newValue) {\n        if (next == null) {\n            next = new List(newValue);\n            return;\n        }\n        next.addToEnd(newValue);\n    }\n}","timestamp":1524244645,"question":"Sp18_Q11_10","feedback":"correct"}]
